Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Subject Files, 2.1.4.3
  - Subject files: Personalities, 1934 - 1973; 22 (Box 1576)
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man in Lowell Thomas's photograph gallery, 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man in Lowell Thomas's photograph gallery], 2
    - [Man in a city (New York?)], 3
    - [Man waving with his hat], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man], 5
    - Note [Ed Cole of General Motors], 6
    - Note [Letter to Lowell Thomas from the International Platform Association], 7
    - Note [List of Officers and the Board of Governors], 8
    - Note [Letter to Lowell Thomas from Dan T. Moore], 9
    - Note [Put captions on-- (?) Patterson, Grimm, Mrs. Patterson, Mrs. T Fref Clatk, Mrs. Clrak, L.T., Mrs. Nathan, Mrs (?) Robert Moses], 10
    - Note [Letter to Lowell Thomas from Maurice J. Murphy], 11
  - Subject files: Personalities, undated; 23 (Box 1576)
    - [Lowell Thomas and a woman talking at the table], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas signing his book for a man], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man looking at a map], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas and a woman sitting on a couch], 5
    - Note [Lewis W. Dymond and Lowell Thomas discussed future plans for Frontier Airlines], 6
    - Note [Note to Phil Benth (?); page 1], 7
    - Note [Note to Phil Benth (?); page 2], 8
    - Note [Note to Phil Benth (?); page 3], 9
    - Note [Clas- (?) Keller, Phil (?)], 10
    - Note [King Feisal A Saudi Arabia who was later assassinated], 11
    - Note [Take to town and give to Joe Dougherty ], 12
    - Note [Photos with captions], 13
    - Note [Sketches of (?) T. (?) and Frank Sinatra], 14
    - Note [illegible], 15
  - Subject files: Personalities, 1962 - 1973; 24 (Box 1576)
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man preparing for an NBC broadcast], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and a woman], 2
    - [Man riding on a horse], 3
    - Note [Letter to Lowell Thomas from Anthony De Lorenzo, Vice President of General Motors Corporation], 4
    - Note [Hilton on Horse], 5
  - Subject files: Personalities: Broadcasters, undated; 25 (Box 1576)
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting on a couch with three other men], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and two men on a couch], 2
    - Note [Floyd Gibbons (eye patch) w/ LT], 3
    - Note [Westbrook Peglar (left) noted columnest, LT, "Buzz" LaQuotte, Hoyd Gibbons], 4
    - Note [R Jwat (?) + Allen Jackson -..(?) eastern (?)], 5
  - Subject files: Personalities: Entertainers, circa 1963 - 1974; 26 (Box 1576)
    - [Lowell Thomas with a woman], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas with a woman], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas and a woman doing a CBS broacast], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas and woman], 4
  - Subject files: Personalities: Foreign Statesmen, undated; 27 (Box 1576)
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting with a foreign statesman], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas at a table with foreign statesmen], 2
    - Note [Philippine President], 3
  - Subject files: Personalities: Military, circa 1950; 28 (Box 1576)
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting with a member of the military], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man preparing for a broadcast], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas with two members of the military], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas and a woman looking at a map], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas and a woman looking at a map], 5
    - Note [L.T. and General Ralph Roya (?)], 6
    - Note [Gene Bullons (?)], 7
    - Note [McArthur, L.T., Tokyo], 8
  Box 1577 - Box 1581
- Subject Files, 2.1.4.3